<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="acolyte_bg">
        <b>Skill Proficiencies:</b> Insight, religion
        \n<b>Languages:</b> Two of your choice
        \n<b>Equipment:</b> A holy symbol, a prayer book or wheel, 5 sticks of incense, vestments, a set of common clothes, and a belt pouch containing 15 gp

        \n\n<b>Feature:</b> Shelter of the Faithful
        As an acolyte, you command the respect of those who share your faith, and you can perform the religious ceremonies of your deity.
        You and your adventuring companions can expect to receive free healing and care at a temple, shrine, or other established presence of your faith,
        though you must provide any material components needed for spells. Those who share your religion will support you (but only you) at a modest lifestyle.

        \n\nYou might also have ties to a specific temple dedicated to your chosen deity or pantheon, and you have a residence there.
        This could be the temple where you used to serve, or a temple where you have found a new home. While near your temple, you can call upon the priests for assistance,
        provided the assistance you ask for is not hazardous and you remain in good standing with your temple.
    </string>
    <string name="criminal_bg">
        <b>Skill Proficiencies:</b> Deception, Stealth
        \n<b>Tool Proficiencies:</b> One type of gaming set, thieves’ tools
        \n<b>Equipment:</b> A crowbar, a set of dark common clothes including a hood, and a belt pouch containing 15 GP.

        \n\n<b>Feature:</b> Criminal Contact
        You have a reliable and trustworthy contact who acts as your liaison to a network of other criminals. You know how to get messages to and from your contact,
        even over great distances; specifically, you know the local messengers, corrupt caravan masters, and seedy sailors who can deliver messages for you.

        \n\n<b>Variant:</b> Spy
        Although your capabilities are not much different from those of a burglar or smuggler, you learned and practiced them in a very different context: as an espionage agent.
        You might have been an officially sanctioned agent of the crown, or perhaps you sold the secrets you uncovered to the highest bidder.
    </string>
</resources>