<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Elf-->
<resources>
    <string name="elf">
        <b>ASI:</b> +2 Dexterity
        \n<b>Size:</b> Medium
        \n<b>Speed:</b> 30 ft
        \n<b>Darkvision:</b> You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can not discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.
        \n<b>Keen Senses:</b> You have proficiency in Perception.
        \n<b>Fey Ancestry:</b> You have advantage on saves against being charmed, and magic can not put you to sleep.
        \n<b>Trance:</b> Elves meditate deeply, remaining semiconscious, for 4 hours a day in place of sleeping. You gain the same benefit that a human does from 8 hours of sleep.
        \n<b>Languages:</b> You can speak, read, and write Common and Elvish.
    </string>
    <string name="wood_elf">
        <b>ASI:</b> Your Wisdom score increases by 1.
        \n<b>Elf Weapon Training:</b> You have proficiency with the longsword, shortsword, shortbow, and longbow.
        \n<b>Fleet of Foot:</b> Your base walking speed increases to 35 feet.
        \n<b>Mask of the Wild:</b> You can attempt to hide even when you are only lightly obscured by foliage, heavy rain, falling snow, mist, and other natural phenomena.
    </string>

<!--Dwarf-->
    <string name="dwarf">
        <b>ASI:</b> +2 Constitution
        \n<b>Size:</b> Medium
        \n<b>Speed:</b> 25 feet. Your speed is not reduced by wearing heavy armor
        \n<b>Darkvision:</b> You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can\'t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray
        \n<b>Dwarven Resilience:</b> You have advantage on saving throws against being poisoned, and you have resistance against poison damage
        \n<b>Dwarven Combat Training:</b> You have proficiency with the battleaxe, handaxe, light hammer, and warhammer
        \n<b>Tool Proficiency:</b> You gain proficiency with one of smith\'s tools, brewer\'s supplies, or mason\'s tools
        \n<b>Stonecunning:</b> Whenever you make a History check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus
        \n<b>Languages:</b> You can speak, read, and write Common and Dwarvish
    </string>
    <string name="hill_dwarf">
        <b>ASI:</b> +1 Wisdom
        \n<b>Dwarven Toughness:</b> Your hit point maximum increases by 1, and it increases by 1 every time you gain a level.
    </string>
</resources>